我开这个员工会议是因为
I called this staff meeting because lately,
餐厅小家庭成员最近渐行渐远
I've noticed our diner family is drifting apart.
干得好 各位 继续努力
Good work, everybody. Good work.
今日的会议就从
Let's start off this powwow
互相分享每个人本周的最高与最低点吧
by sharing our highs and lows of the week.
我的最高点是学到了一个很有趣的冷知识
My high was getting a particularly interesting Snapple fact.
而我的最低点是...
And my low was--
你全身的高度吗
Your entire body?
我来分享
I'll go.
我的最高点是在厕所里捡到了一个发夹
My high was finding a barrette in the bathroom,
而最低点是想象新人生中没有它
and my low was imagining my new life without it.
麦克斯 你的最高点呢
Max, your high?
我正高[嗨]着呢
I certainly am.
而最低点则是在药效过了的那一刻
And my low will be when it wears off.
我的最高点是瞄到一眼
Well, my high was catching a glimpse
顾客的蕾丝丁字裤
of a customer's lacy g-string,
而最低点是我看到他鸡鸡的时刻
And my low was seeing his junk.
我的最低点就是参加这会议
My low is this meeting.
而最高点就是会议结束的那一刻
And my high is when it wraps up.
还能不能认真地开会啦
Can everybody take this serious--
我有个新低点了
I have a new low.
-我也有个新高点了 -我也是
- I have a new high. - Me too.
大家别这样好吗
Everybody, please.
人家阿憨明显是伤到"小洞洞"了
Han just clearly injured his vagina.
不是我的电话响
That's not my phone.
你知道我的铃声是《冰雪奇缘》"随它吧"
My ringtone is Let it go, and you know that
因为每次响起来你都恐吓要揍我
'cause you threaten to beat me every time it rings.
也不是我的
Well, it's not mine.
我的电话永远保持震动模式
I keep my phone on vibrate
一方面是尊重我周围的人
out of respect for those around me,
一方面也是给自己点小"高潮"
and also for little orgasms.
麦克斯 是座机
Max, it's the landline.
天啊 它为什么在响
Oh, God! Why is it ringing?
你说过这电话只有在我们有麻烦时才会响
You said that phone only rings if we're in trouble
或者是未来的你打电话来
or if it's you calling from the future
通知我们有麻烦了
to tell us we're in trouble.
惨喽
Ruh-roh.
肯定是房东 租约要到期了
That's gotta be the landlord. The lease is up.
好吧 那就续约吧 虽然我以为
Fine, we'll just renew it, even though I thought
他们早该报废这栋楼了
they would have condemned this place by now.
毕竟我昨天还在走廊看到"报废"的套套呢
I mean, I did find a used condom in the hallway yesterday.
-您好 -不行
- Hello? - No!
快挂掉 我们俩没在租约上
Hang up. We're not on the lease.
编的不错 现在我们就祈祷
Good cover. Now we just have to hope
原来的租客是个日式铁板烧厨师吧
the original tenant is a Benihana chef.
好
Okay.
我们时间不多 快点
We don't have much time. Quick!
选两样你爱的东西 拿上跑
Grab two things you love.
这里没有我爱的东西
I-I love nothing in here!
而且为毛我们要试着留住
And why are we even trying to keep an apartment
一间浴室里长草的破公寓啊
that has grass growing in the bathroom?
我爱我们的浴室草坪
I love our toilet lawn.
恶心死了
It's gross.
麦克斯 看看这里
Max, look at this place.
我们冰箱的门是用透明胶带固定住的
Our refrigerator door is held on by scotch tape,
那里面还长黑霉了呢
And, I mean, there is black mold in there.
但至少黑霉把其他种霉菌
At least the black mold made the other mold
都赶出这一带了呢
move out of the neighborhood.
乖嘛
Come on!
不动产公司估计已经派人来
Someone from the real estate company
检查一下租下这间屋的租客
is probably on their way over to make sure
是不是还住在这里
the original tenant still lives here.
好了 开溜吧
All right, let's ride!
我认识一个人 可以把做好的假护照
I know a guy that can drop off some fake passports
放在机场的置物箱里给我们
for us in an airport locker.
那个人你也认识 就是奥列格
Well, you know him too. It's Oleg.
行行好 接起电话吧
Pick up that phone already!
听起来像PBS台募款活动的捐款来电呢
Sounds like a damn PBS fund-raiser down here.
苏菲 是房东打来
Sophie, it's the landlord calling.
我才发现原来这里是非法转租来的
I just found out we've been subletting illegally.
我早就好奇你俩
Oh, well, I always wondered how you girls
是怎么付得起这里的房租
could afford to live in this building.
但在看过卡洛琳的舞技后 我确定了不是做鸡
And I ruled out prostitution once I saw Caroline dance.
有好消息
Good news.
我在公寓里四处翻翻后
I dug around the apartment
我找到了原来的租约
And I found the original lease.
还找到了我出生证明的副本
Also found a copy of my birth certificate.
原来我老爸的名字是"老妈不知道"
Turns out my father's name is "Mother has no idea"
不用管那租约了
Forget that lease.
我已经为我们找到新家了
I've already found a new place for us.
曼哈顿 两间卧室 只要一千三
A two-bedroom for $1,300 in Manhattan.
慢着 是堪萨斯州的曼哈顿
Oh... Manhattan, Kansas.
这租约一定得保住
We can't afford to lose this lease.
只要他们发现莱斯特·唐纳文
As soon as they find out this Lester Donovan
已经不住在这里 租金就会涨
is no longer living there, the rent will get higher
涨到像比伯跟他老爸在飞机上一样嗨[高]
than Justin Bieber on a plane with his dad.
所以我找到了这个原租客 莱斯特
So I tracked down this original tenant guy, Lester.
他还活着
He's still alive.
真是没完没了啊
Ugh! Can't catch a break.
他住在布鲁克林区一家养老院里
He's at a rest home in Sheepshead Bay.
我们只需要去把他绑架来就行了
We just have to go there and kidnap him.
把一碗老人小麦粥绑鱼竿上 再钓他出来
We'll tie some cream of wheat to a pole and lure him out.
首先 在哪个平行时空里
First of all, in what world
咱俩有钱买老人小麦粥鱼竿
do we have cream of wheat pole money?
第二 我才不要去勒索一个老头子
And secondly, I am not gonna go shake down some old man.
才不需要自己动手
You won't have to.
那老头估计都自己在抖[勒索]了
He's probably already shaking.
如果你们在找房 我知道一个地方
If you're looking, I know a place.
你们跟另外两个妞分享一张双人床
You share a twin bed with two other girls.
而且里面还有摄像机
Oh, and there are cameras.
但你每分钟能赚到4块99
But you're paid $4.99 a minute
而且还有机会认识附近所有单身痴汉
and get to meet all the singles in your area.
你也是"附近的单身痴汉"中的一员吗
Are you one of the singles in the area?
正确来说 我是你的合演者
Technically I'd be your costar.
无论你喜不喜欢 我们的公寓都得保住
Like it or not, we have to hold on to our apartment.
麦克斯说得对 世上有两样东西不能失去
Max is right--there are two things in life you cannot lose.
受租金管制的公寓 与自己的膀胱控制力
A rent-controlled apartment and bladder control.
其实我大楼里有一间公寓
Actually, there's an apartment in my building
整好要出租呢
that just became available.
明天有空来看看
Stop by tomorrow. You can see it.
这里要一千二啊
This place is $1,200?
一千二百五 就在我们说话时又涨价了
$1,250. It just went up since we been talking.
这里对我们来说太挤了
We can't fit in here.
"我们"指的不是我和你
I'm not talking about me and you.
是我和我的巨乳
I'm talking about me and my boobs.
挺不错的养老院啊
Nice retirement home.
我们为何不就住这里呢
Why don't we just live here?
宾果游戏大赛 无限量的硬糖果
Bingo tournaments, unlimited hard candy,
而且想在裤子里拉屎就拉屎
and you get to crap your pants!
莱斯特
Lester?
这估计就是他了
That must be him.
我已不知道我是谁 但那肯定是他
I don't know who I am anymore, but that must be him.
你好 唐纳文先生
Hi, Mr. Donovan.
莱斯特
Lester?
麦克斯 他是不是死了
Max, is he dead?
还活着 但也就剩一口气了
No, he's alive, but just...
太可怜了
This is so sad.
看看老年人都是怎么被对待的
Look at how we treat our elderly.
快醒来
Wake up!
我需要你醒过来
I-I-I need you to wake up for this!
我们是你以前公寓的转租客
We are currently subletting your old apartment,
我们需要你回去假装
and we need you to pretend
你还住里面 一天就行
tou still live there for a day.
或者假装一下你还活着
Or just to pretend you still live.
姑娘们 你们是在浪费时间
Ladies, you're wasting your time.
他不能说话 也不喜欢姑娘
He can't speak, and he doesn't like girls.
他是个植物人[蔬菜]加基佬[水果]
He's a vegetable and a fruit.
我是莱斯特·唐纳文
Lester Donovan.
你才是莱斯特啊 谢天谢地
Oh, you're Lester! Oh, thank God.
莱斯特 我们需要你...
Listen, Lester, we need you--
我知道 你们想我回去假装
I know, I know. You want me to pretend
还住在你们公寓里 我在外头都听到了
I still live in your apartment. I overheard everything.
亲爱的 我们不是每个人都在昏迷中
We're not all comatose, darling.
但很抱歉 姑娘们 我可能帮不上忙了
But I'm afraid--ahem-- it's not gonna happen, girls.
我这周有大事要忙
'cause I got a big week.
我的心上人要搬来跟我同居了
My special lady is moving in with me.
因为这家伙活不了多久了
'Cause this guy's not gonna be around much longer.
最多再活18小时
18 hours...tops!
我的公主来啦
Oh! Here's my princess.
奥利维亚
Olivia!
上帝保佑 他还活着
He's still with us. God bless.
所以你的搬家大计得挪到周一了
So we'll have to push the move to Monday.
说到这件事 莱斯特
Yeah... about that, Lester.
我还没做好搬来同居的心理准备
I'm not ready to move in with you.
奥利维亚 你这话什么意思
Olivia, wh--what do you mean?
-麦克斯 我们该走了 - 才不要
- Max, we should go. - No way!
这就像在看老年人版的《单身汉》一样
This is like watching an elder version of The Bachelor!
现在基本就是最终环节了呢
Literally... The final rose!
莱斯特 问题不在你 在我
Lester, it's not you. It's me.
他们这把年纪还用这招吗
That's still in play at their age?
我还不想定下来
I'm just not ready to settle down.
林中太多鸟 海中太多鱼
Too many other fish in the sea.
我知道了 是新搬进来的那小混球对吧
I know--it's about that new kid on the block,
莫蒂 啥来着 是因为那个莫蒂对吧
Morty what's-his-name. It's about Morty, isn't it?
莱斯特 别这样
Lester, please.
我不想之后我们在
I don't want it to be weird
宾果游戏见面时变得很尴尬
when we see each other at bingo.
我告诉你 莫蒂这家伙
You should know this about Morty--
不是我这样的真汉子
he's not a real man like me.
他的中间名是伟哥好吗
His middle name is Viagra!
奥利维亚
Olivia!
现在也没必要留在这里了
Well, there's no point hanging around here.
我去拿上我的阴茎帮浦就能走了
I'll just grab my penis pump, and we're outta here.
他为什么会需要用到那个
Why is he gonna need that?
到啦 "甜美温馨
Here we are, "home, sweet...
至少不是养老院的家里"
at least it's not a rest home""
莱斯特 虽然我不介意推着你走了足足35条街
Lester, not that I minded pushing you 35 blocks, but...
但是你在养老院时还能走路
you could walk at the home.
为什么现在不能走路了
why can't you walk now?
内心苦闷走不了路
I'm too depressed to walk.
我从学会走路时就一直苦闷
I've been depressed since I learned to walk.
那时我九岁 也是时候了
I mean, I was nine. It was time.
我刚失去了我一生挚爱
I have just lost the love of my life!
你跟没牙齿还装有人工屁股的妞
Have you ever made love to a lady with no teeth
做爱过吗
and two plastic hips?
小女子我就没试过
I, for one, have not.
麦克斯呢
Max?
没 但这事直接登上了我死前愿望的第一名了
No. But it just rocketed to number one on my bucket list.
这里我从54年住到54俱乐部的时代[77年]
I lived here from 1954 to studio 54.
丽莎·明尼利曾在那角落呕吐
Liza Minnelli threw up in that corner.
我的人生中唯一一次看到
The only time I ever saw anybody
有人在呕吐后还三鞠躬谢幕的
take three bows after a vomit.
那你为什么离开了
Why did you leave?
人总是觉得能找到更好的
You always think you're gonna find something better.
浴室芳草绿 隔岸风景好
Yep. The toilet grass is always greener.
大楼物业代表来了 莱斯特
Okay. That's the building rep, Lester.
需要再复习一下假的背景故事吗
Do we need to go over our cover story again?
很简单的
It's pretty easy.
我是卡洛塔·伊搭丽面
I'm Carlotta Spaghetta...
白天是个温柔的宠物训练师
Mild-mannered pet trainer by day,
晚上是脾气火爆的尼日利亚间谍
hot-tempered Nigerian spy by night.
莱斯特 听我的就好
Lester, only listen to me.
麦克斯是你的孙女
Max is your granddaughter,
而我是她的戒酒陪护员
and I'm her sober companion--
整段故事中只有这是真的
which is the only part of our story that's true.
他来了 你就坐着 微笑 点头即可
It's him--now, just sit and smile and nod.
我可以点头 但我才不微笑
I'll nod, but I'm not gonna smile.
欢迎来到我爷爷
Welcome to my grandfather's
欢乐幸福的家 那是他的沙发
happy, happy home. There's his couch.
那是他的厨房
There's his kitchen.
这是什么
What's this?
那是他的大麻烟斗
There's his bong.
他抽大麻吗
His bong.
-青光眼缓解 -化疗止痛
- Glaucoma. - Chemo.
好吧 下午好
Well, good afternoon.
我是大楼管理派来的 我叫罗杰
I'm Roger from building management.
我是来核实租约的
I'm here to verify this lease,
我想要在
and I'd like to do it
这走廊坍塌前就搞定这件事
before the rest of this doorway caves in.
想必你肯定认识我
And of course you know my dear,
最最亲爱的爷爷莱斯特
dear grandfather Lester.
我就循例问几个问题 唐纳文先生
I just have a few questions, Mr. Donovan.
你有没有试过跟硅胶屁屁的女人做爱
Have you ever made love to a woman with a silicone hip?
超爽的哦
It's amazing!
好的 我可以把这条从我清单上划掉了
Okay! I can cross that one off my list.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我之所以从后门进来
I came through the back
是因为那个瘾君子在前门台阶那
'cause this junkie's on the front stoop,
而且我们之间还有点小尴尬
and it's still a little awkward between us.
这位是苏菲 她住在楼上
Oh, uh, this is Sophie. She lives upstairs.
你也看到了 罗杰 没有任何问题
As you can see, Roger, no problems.
一切完全合法
Everything's totally legit.
这老头是谁
Hey, who's the old guy?
她住在楼上 而她居然不认识莱斯特
She lives upstairs, and she doesn't know Lester?
当然认识 这只是他们常玩的一个性爱游戏
She knows him--this is just a sexual game they play
名叫"你是谁"
called "Who are you?"
那语气听起来可不像在玩性游戏
That doesn't sound like a sexual game.
等她冲着他的鸡鸡问时就像了
It is when she's saying it to his penis.
苏菲 这是房地产公司的人
Sophie, this is the guy from the agency
他是过来核实
who just came by to verify
莱斯特是否真的住在这里
that Lester actually lives here.
当然
Oh, yeah!
他每天都住在这里
He lives here every day!
而且我们一直在玩这游戏
Yeah, and we play that game forever.
你是谁呀
Who are you?
靠近点 他听不见
Come closer. He can't hear you.
我已经感觉好多了
I'm feeling better already.
所以主要的信息就是
So the main takeaway here
他们是这栋楼的合法居民
is that they both live in the building legally.
赶紧签租约吧
Now, let's just sign that lease.
唐纳文先生 麻烦您在这里签字
Mr. Donovan, I just need your signature here,
这份房租的合约期是四年
and this'll lock you into the lease for another four years.
你的屁屁状况如何
What's your hip situation?
纯天然不加料 宝贝
Oh, I'm as hip as they come, baby! Yeah!
真是个美人呀
Now, that's a looker!
-签好了 -手续办好了
- Here ya go. - Yep! All done.
你还可以在这里多住四年
You have the apartment for another four years.
好好享用
Enjoy it?
按要求我得告知你们 这里有些公寓
Oh, and I'm required to say: Traces of cancerous stuff
被发现有致癌物
have been found in some of the apartments.
祝你们愉快
Have a nice day!
再住四年 再住四年
Four more years! Four more years!
我们还能继续住在这里
We get to stay in the place
一个我从不认为我会想住的地方
I never thought I'd want to stay in.
莱斯特 你起来啦 感觉好点了吗
Oh, Lester, you're up. Feeling better?
感觉棒极了
Like a million bucks.
仿佛我又变回原来的自己
I feel like my old self again.
已经过了18小时了
Oh, hey, it's been 18 hours.
我们快回去看看你室友死了没
Let's go see if your friend's dead.
对 莱斯特 我们送你回家吧
Yeah, Lester. Let's get ya home.
你们瞎说什么 我现在就在家
What are you talking about? I am home.
你在瞎说什么 这是我们的家
What do you mean? This is our place.
刚才我签的那份租约可不是这么说的哦
Not according to that lease I just signed.
我要回我的房间了
I'll be in my bedroom.
回家的感觉真好
Good to be home!
-惨喽 -惨喽
- Ruh-roh... - Ruh-roh.
姑娘们 这太好吃了
Ladies, this is delicious!
在养老院 他们都把盐锁起来了
You know, at the home they keep salt on lockdown.
同被锁的还有痴呆病人
Salt and the dementia patients.
看来这贼老头今晚是不会走了
Well, it doesn't look like bad grandpa's leaving tonight.
或许我可以帮忙
Maybe I can help.
我可以在他牛肉饼里放点毛玻璃
I can put some ground glass in his salisbury steak.
这称为乌克兰式离婚
It's called a Ukrainian divorce.
我还是先试试果冻好了
Eh...I'll try this jell-o first.
是啊 过期了那么久 没准能毒死他
Yeah, it's so old, it might kill him.
莱斯特 请你吃果冻啊
Lester, I brought you some jell-o.
-想吃吗 -你真好
- Would you like some? - That's very nice of you,
但我是不会走的
but I'm not going anywhere.
莱斯特 说真的 你不会想跟我们住的
Lester, really, you don't want to live with us.
卡洛琳经常唱歌
Caroline sings so much
她身边应该有一只卡通鸟
she should have animated birds on her.
听着 我是绝对不会回养老院的
Look, there's no way I'm going back to that retirement home.
这是去年我曾短暂挂掉后
I feel alive for the first time since...
头一次觉得自己还活着
since I died briefly last year.
天啊 真的吗
Oh, my God, really?
是的 某个护士把电线碰掉了
Yes, some nurse tripped over the power cord.
再说了 在这里能帮我忘记奥利维亚
A-and besides, it's really helping me get over Olivia.
我也终于意识到 大海里多的是其他的"鱼"
I'm finally realizing there are plenty of other fish in the sea.
各位安安
Hey, everybody!
她就是其中一条大鱼
And there's one of 'em.
鲈鱼中的翘臀鱼
She puts the "ass" in "bass."
朋友 我去我的卡座啦
Friend, I'll be in my booth.
苏菲 你还记得莱斯特吧
Hey, Sophie. You remember Lester.
莱斯特 你还记得火是什么时候发现的吧
Lester, you remember when they discovered fire.
快请快请 坐我这
Please, please, join me.
我能请你喝蛋蜜乳吗
May I buy you an egg cream?
我超爱喝"蛋"蜜乳的
Oh, I do love an egg cream.
抱歉 我要去一下洗手间
Oh, excuse me, I gotta go powder by nose.
姑娘们
Girls...
姑娘们 我知道你们想要回你们的公寓
Girls, I know you want your apartment back
我是一个讲理的人
and I'm a reasonable man,
所以我离开的条件是 你们懂的
so all I want before I go is a little you-know-what.
更多果冻吗
More jell-o?
我说的是做爱 疗情伤性爱
I'm talking about sex. Rebound sex!
疗情伤性爱吗
Rebound sex?
你确定你做完爱后 你还能直起身[疗伤]来吗
Are you sure you'll even be able to rebound from having sex?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
养老院里除了做爱就没别的
There's nothing but sex at that retirement home.
不然你以为我干嘛要进去
Why do you think I put myself there?
在那里可以随时随地做爱
It's wall-to-wall whoopee,
而且完事后还不用开车回家
and you don't even have to drive home after.
我已经有人选了 是一位优雅的女士
Now, I have in mind a certain elegant lady.
妈的 你们的厕纸用完了
Ahh, you're out of T.P.!
你帮我牵线和你的朋友共度一晚
You can set me up for one night with your friend,
然后我将很乐意离开
and I will gladly leave the apartment.
我去你的卡座等你
I'll be in your booth.
苏菲 你能忍受和那老头上床 对吧
Hey, Sophie, you'll get with that old guy, right?
你他妈开什么玩笑啊
Are you fricking kidding me?
莱斯特 她不愿意
Lester, she didn't go for it.
那我不要拖着我两腿之间的"尾巴"
I'm not going back to that retirement home
灰溜溜地回养老院
with my tail between my legs.
我一定要跟某人上床 好让奥利维亚嫉妒
I gotta sleep with someone to make Olivia jealous.
其实呢 有一种新事物叫做"撒谎"
There's a new thing that kids are doing called "Lying."
你就不能瞎编点什么吗
Why don't you just make something up?
无图无真相
Pics or it didn't happen.
我要跟每一个我勾搭的人拍一张自拍照
I need a selfie with whoever I hook up with
放到我脸书的主页上
for my facebook page.
如果那个人不是苏菲
And if it's not gonna be Sophie,
我猜床上的只能是你们俩其中一个了
my guess, it's gonna be one of you two up in bed...
强打者
Slugger.
强打者[棒球]
* 带我去看球赛 *
* Take me out to the ball game *
* 带我去 *
* Take me out *
现在我知道丽莎为什么会吐了
Now I know why Liza threw up.
现在换我内心苦闷了
Now I'm depressed.
你不过是抽签
So you lost the straw pull
不幸抽中了要跟莱斯特上床嘛
for who's gonna sleep with Lester.
听着 一直说想做爱的人是你
Look, you've been saying you wanted to have sex
一直说想买古董的人也是你
and you've also been saying you wanna go antiquing.
现在打开门 即可拥有这两者
So, behind that door are both.
麦克斯 我觉得你抽签时作弊了
And, Max, I think you cheated in that straw pull.
我当然作弊啦
Of course I cheated!
我虽然做过很多疯狂的爱
Look, I have had a lot of crazy sex.
我曾经在葬礼上跟一个小丑做爱
I once did it with a clown at a funeral.
但我无法直视那个阴茎帮浦
But I cannot see that penis pump.
我会一辈子做恶梦的
I won't be able to come back from that.
那你觉得我不会吗
You think I can?
是的 我觉得你大脑科学那部分会很喜欢那玩意
I do, I think the science part of your brain would enjoy it.
姑娘们 我做完伸展运动了
Ladies, I've stretched.
可以开始了
I'm ready.
好吧 这颗子弹我来挡
Fine, I'll take the bullet.
我觉得他那把"枪"也没"子弹"了
I don't think there are any bullets in that gun.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我可不想怀上一个老宝宝
'cause I don't wanna have an old baby.
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous
我们都开始自娱自乐了
that we're even entertaining the thought
无论跟那老头干嘛 都不是妙招好吗
of doing anything with an old man that isn't a trump.
麦克斯 我做不到
Max, I can't do this.
看来我们俩有一人
One of us will just have to take
得去厄尔楼里的公寓住
that apartment in Earl's building
而你就另找住处吧啊
and you will find another place.
但这样的话 我们就要分开了
But then we'd have to live apart.
我知道 但别无选择
I know, but I don't see another choice.
可我还不想跟你分开
I'm not ready to live without you.
我也还不想跟你分开
怎么了
What?
我看见那帮浦了 你收拾东西滚蛋吧
I saw the pump! Pack your things!
麦克斯 真不敢相信你为了不跟我分开
Max, I can't believe you were almost willing to do that
差点就牺牲了自己
to live with me.
我太感动了 这次换我来
You know what, I'm going in.
因为想到不能一周七天
Because the thought of not seeing you
一天二十四小时都见到你 我就难过得要死
24 hours a day, 7 days a week, would kill me!
我们还是每周六早上一起喝咖啡好了
We'll meet every Saturday morning for coffee.
当然相聚会随着时间越来越少
Less and less over time, of course.
挺不错的开始 你们俩还有什么招
That was a good start. What else you got?
没了
Nothing!
我现在真的好喜欢从"后门"进
Ah, I'm really liking this whole back door thing.
这是我第一次说这种话
Wow, that's the first time I've ever said that.
别变成习惯了 苏菲
Don't get used to it, Sophie.
你从没有过
You never do.
不 我是说我们要离开这间公寓了
No, I mean, we're gonna have to leave this place.
我们实在没办法跟莱斯特上床
We couldn't do it with Lester.
我知道 所以我来了
I know, that's why I'm here.
你不必为了我们这样做
You don't have to do this for us.
如果你们俩离开了这栋楼
If you two didn't live in this building,
那我们会渐行渐远
then we'd drift apart
只能在每周六早上喝咖啡的时候见个面
and we'd only see each other on Saturdays for coffee.
而我 大概只会去一次吧
Well... I'd probably only go once.
给我90秒
Look, just give me 90 seconds.
这家伙都得用辅助工具 能有多难[硬]呢
I mean, he's got a pump. How hard could it be?
她太见义勇为了
She's amazing.
我们应该送她点东西作为报答
We should probably get her something for this.
送什么合适呢
What would be appropriate?
水槽下面那根好蜡烛吗
That good candle under the sink?
我们只用过一次
We've only used it once.
就送那个吧
That seems right.
我不知道那是什么 但我无福消受
I don't know what that was, but I'm not up to it.
我觉得我的心脏会招架不住
I-I don't think my heart could take it.
担心跟苏菲做爱会害死你吗
Afraid sex with Sophie would kill you?
没错 所以我才没这么做
Yeah, that's why I haven't gone there.
虽然我对海里多的是其他鱼
You know, I was all excited about--about all the--
感到十分性奋
all the other fish in the sea.
但里面那条可是大白鲨啊
That was a great white shark!
快进来
Hey, come on!
伸展运动完毕 可以开始了
I just stretched. I'm ready.
要不我们来拍张照好了
Look, uh, could we get a quick pic?
早知道他有iPhone 5s 我就牺牲一下了
I might've gone there, too, if I knew he had an iPhone 5s.
-尽量性感一点 -好的
- Try to be as sexy as possible. - Oh, okay, yeah.
当奥利维亚看见这照片时 她肯定不会再想着莫蒂
When Olivia sees that, she's gonna say, "Morty who?"
姑娘们 好好享用这间公寓
Girls, enjoy your apartment.
我在这里过得很愉快
I had some lovely times here.
非常感谢你 莱斯特
Thank you so much, Lester.
再见 爷爷
Bye, grandpa.
或许有时间我们可以去养老院看你
Maybe sometime we could come visit you in the home.
发电邮给我 到时候再说
Email me. We'll talk.
他这把年纪还用这招吗
That's still in play at his age?
谢谢你让我没爽到啊 莱斯特
Hey, thanks for the blue balls, Lester!
安安啦 姑娘们
Nighty-night, girls.
麦克斯 我们又可以在一起了
Max, we get to stay together!
更棒的是 他忘了把轮椅带走了
And even better, He left his wheelchair!
推我进厨房 我要开一瓶啤酒喝
Push me into the kitchen, I wanna crack open a beer.
不知道你70岁的时候 我会不会像这样帮你推轮椅
I wonder if I'll be pushing you like this when you're 70.
我30岁的时候 你就可以帮我推轮椅了
You'll be pushing me like this when I'm 30.
金窝银窝比不上自己的狗窝
There's no place like home.
我去拿透明胶带
I'll go get the scotch tape.